Finding Aid for Museum of Art (University of Michigan) records, 1946-2003
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Exhibition Files, 1946-2003
  - 1995-1996
    - "Painting with Fire: Pewabic Vessels in the Margaret Watson Parker Collection,", September 23, 1995-January 7, 1996 (Box 13)
    - "Stitched, Layered and Pieced: Michigan Artists and the Quilt,", October 14-December 10, 1995 (Box 13)
    - "'Unpainted to the Last': Moby-Dick and American Art, 1930-1990,", November 4-December 24, 1995 (Box 14)
      (Spencer Museum of Art, University of Kansas)
    - "The Interpretation Project,", November 11, 1995-February 11, 1996 (Box 14)
    - "Sol LeWitt: Five Wall Drawings,", January 10-August 4, 1996 (Box 14)
    - "Dark Embrace: Images of War, Death and Apocalypse,", January 20-March 17, 1996 (Box 14)
    - "Trio: Masterpieces of Contemporary Japanese Ceramic Art,", February 17-April 14, 1996 (Box 14)
      (The Field Museum and Consulate-General of Japan at Chicago)
    - "Bold Strokes: The Inventiveness of Rembrandt's Late Prints,", February 24-April 28, 1996 (Box 14)
    - "Folk and Outsider Art: An Ann Arbor Collection,", March 29-June 16, 1996 (Box 14)
    - "Kukuli Velarde: Homage to My Heart,", April 2-May 12, 1996 (Box 14)
      (University of Michigan Institute for the Humanities and UMMA)
    - "American Photographs,", May 4-June 23, 1996 (Box 14)
    - "The Weddige Collection: A Gift to the University,", May 10-July 7, 1996 (Box 14)
    - "The New American: Carl Demeulenaere,", July 6-August 18, 1996 (Box 14)
    - "Beaux-Arts Visions: Architectural Renderings by Herbert W. Johe,", July 13-August 25, 1996 (Box 14)
    - "Albert Kahn: An American Architect Abroad,", July 13-September 8, 1996 (Box 14)
    - "Common Ground: African Art and Affinities,", July 20, 1996-January 1997 (Box 14)
      (includes exhibition guidesheet)
  - 1996-1997
    - "Venice, Traditions Transformed: Works from the Sarah Campbell Blaffer Foundation and the University of Michigan,", September 21, 1996-January 12, 1997; 3 folders (Box 14)
      (Museum of Fine Arts, Houston and UMMA)
      (includes catalogue)
    - "Sustenance, Sociability and Ceremony: The Art of Eating in Global Perspective,", October 19-November 17, 1996 (Box 14)
    - "Images d'Epinal,", November 2, 1996-January 5, 1997; 2 folders (Box 14)
      (Musée du Québec)
      (includes label copy and color copies of installation photographs)
    - "Ellen Driscoll. Ahab's Wife: Working Drawings and Models,", February 1-March 16, 1997 (Box 14)
      (includes label copy and correspondence with the artist)
    - "Museum Collects: 20th Century Works on Paper" (Part I), February 1-May 4, 1997 (Box 14)
    - "Michigan Collectors" (Works from the collections of graduates and friends of the University), February 8-April 13, 1997 (Box 14)
    - "Floating Pictures" (Japanese prints from the permanent collections), March 29-June 1, 1997 (Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous future exhibitions (Box 14)
    - "Faculty Artists Exhibition,", May 3-August 3, 1997 (Box 15)
    - "Marcel Monceaux," [1997] (Box 15)
    - "Museum Collects: 20th Century Works on Paper" (Part II), May 10-September 14, 1997 (Box 15)
  - 1997-1998
    - "Sepphoris in Galilee: Crosscurrents of Culture,", September 7-December 14, 1997; 3 folders (Box 15)
      (North Carolina Museum of Art)
    - "The Body (Un)Veiled: Boundaries of the Figure in Early Modern Europe,", September 13-October 26, 1997 (Box 15)
    - "Powers That Be, Powers That Seem: African Art from the Curtis Collection,", September 22-October 12, 1997 (Box 15)
    - "Selections from the Lannan Foundation Collection: Paintings, 1958-1978,", October 4, 1997-February 2, 1998 (Box 15)
    - "Spectator of Life: Works by George Bellows from the Sloan Collection" (Doris Sloan Memorial Exhibition), October 4-December 7, 1997; 3 folders (Box 15)
    - "Glances and Gazes of the Social Fantastic: Early 20th Century French Photography,", October 18, 1997-January 4, 1998 (Box 15)
    - "Fifteen Visions: Books by Contemporary Regional Artists,", October 22, 1997-January 4, 1998 (Box 15)
    - "Lost Russia: Photographs by William Craft Brumfield,", November 1, 1997-January 4, 1998 (Box 15)
      (Duke University Museum of Art)
    - "Monet at Vétheuil: The Turning Point,", January 25-March 15, 1998; 8 folders
      (includes 5 audiocassettes from "Monet and the Cultural and Social Milieu of Impressionism" symposium, February 7, 1998)
      - Folders 1-4 (Box 15)
      - (folders 5-8) (Box 16)
    - "Chinese Ceramics from the Permanent Collection,", April 5-July 26, 1998 (Box 16)
    - "Jim Dow: The National League Stadiums,", May 3-September 2, 1998 (Box 16)
    - "Patrick Dougherty: Primitive Ways in an Accelerated World," June 4-?, 1998 (Box 16)
    - "African Arts: Objects of Power, Knowledge, and Mediation," June 4-?, 1998 (Box 16)
  - 1998-1999
    - "Dreamscapes: The Surrealist Impulse" (Doris Sloan Memorial Exhibition), August 22-October 25, 1998; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - "Hopes and Aspirations: Decorative Painting of Korea,", September 18-November 14, 1998 (Box 16)
    - "Master Drawings from the Worcester Art Museum,", November 7, 1998-January 17, 1999 (Box 16)
      (Worcester Art Museum)
    - "Bill Jacobson: Portraits, Songs, Thoughts 1992-1997,", January 30-March 28, 1999 (Box 16)
    - "Magdalena Abakanowicz and the Mindless Crowd,", February 13-May 2, 1999 (Box 16)
    - "Seeing It Through: Faculty Artists from the School of Art and Design,", April 10-July 3, 1999 (Box 16)
      (includes artists' statements and color reproductions)
  - 1999-2000
    - "Touchstone: 200 Years of Artists' Lithographs,", July 17-September 12, 1999 (Box 16)
      (Harvard University Art Museums)
    - "When Time Began to Rant and Rage: Figurative Painting from 20th Century Ireland,", October 25, 1999-January 2, 2000 (Box 16)
    - "The Orchid Pavilion Gathering: Chinese Painting from the University of Michigan Museum of Art,", January 23-March 26, 2000; 3 folders (Box 16)
    - "Transparent/Opaque: An Installation by Annette Lawrence,", March 18-April 16, 2000 (Box 16)
      (includes installation slide)
    - "Still Time: Photographs by Sally Mann,", April 15-June 11, 2000 (Box 16)
    - "The White House Collection of American Crafts,", July 1-October 22, 2000 (Box 16)
    - "Amish Quilts 1880-1940 from the Collection of Faith and Stephen Brown,", July 8-September 10, 2000 (Box 16)
  - 2000-2001 (Box 17)
    - "Arthur Miller at Work: Photographs by Inge Morath,", September 2-November 5, 2000 (Box 17)
    - "Video Art by Chris Doyle," (part of "VideoCulture: Three Decades of Video Art"), September 7-October 4, 2000 (Box 17)
    - "The Villa of the Mysteries in Pompeii: Ancient Ritual, Modern Muse" (UMMA & Kelsey Museum of Archaeology), October 1-November 19, 2000 (Box 17)
    - "Seeing is Healing? The Visual Arts of Medicine,", October 7-December 3, 2000 (Box 17)
    - "Plant Life: Works from the Permanent Collection,", November 18, 2000-January 21, 2001 (Box 17)
    - "Day Without Art,", December 1, 2000 (Box 17)
      (in honor of World AIDS Day)
    - "Mark Rothko and the Lure of the Figure: Paintings 1933-1946,", December 16, 2000-February 25, 2001 (Box 17)
    - "Scenarios: Recent Work by Lorna Simpson,", February 24-May 13, 2001; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - "African Art of Dual Worlds," April 5, 2001-ongoing (Box 17)
    - "Paradise Now: Picturing the Genetic Revolution,", March 17-May 27, 2001 (Box 17)
  - 2001-2002
    - "Albert Kahn: Inspiration for the Modern,", June 2-October 21, 2001; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - "Kemnitz Paints Ann Arbor,", July 14-August 5, 2001 (Box 17)
    - "In Human Touch: Photographs by Ernestine Ruben,", June 10-September 23, 2001; 3 folders (Box 17)
    - "Donald Sultan: The Smoke Rings,", August 18-November 25, 2001 (Box 17)
    - "Japanese Costumes and Ceramics, Past and Present,", Fall 2001 (Box 17)
      (includes docent guide)
    - "Japanese Fishermen's Coats from Awaji Island,", October 13, 2001-January 6, 2002 (Box 17)
      (UCLA Fowler Museum of Cultural History, Los Angeles and University Art Museum, University of California, Santa Barbara)
    - "A Matter of Degree: Abstraction in 20th Century Art,", November 10, 2001-January 27, 2002 (Box 18)
    - "People and Places: The Baker Gift of 20th Century Photography,", December 8, 2001-February 10, 2002 (Box 18)
    - "Women Who Ruled: Queens, Goddesses, Amazons, 1500-1650,", February 17-May 5, 2002; 4 folders (Box 18)
    - "Courtesans, Cross-Dressers and the Girl Next Door: Images of the Feminine in Japanese Popular Prints,", March 8-September 1, 2002 (Box 18)
    - "Kara Walker: An Abbreviated Emancipation (from The Emancipation Approximation),", March 9-May 26, 2002 (Box 18)
    - "Flora and Fauna in Chinese Art," April 6-?, 2002 (Box 18)
      includes label copy
    - "Up Close: Abstract Photography by Howard Bond,", May 18-August 11, 2002 (Box 18)
  - 2002-2003
    - "Picasso: Masterworks from the Collection,", June 8-September 15, 2002 (Box 18)
    - "Lee Bul: Live Forever," [2002] (Box 18)
    - "Ansel Adams: A Centennial Celebration,", July 20-September 22, 2002 (Box 18)
    - "Manuel Alvarez Bravo: 100 Years,", July 20-October 13, 2002 (Box 18)
    - "The New York School: Abstract Expressionism and Beyond,", July 20, 2002-January 19, 2003 (Box 18)
    - "A Bold Experiment: Ken Tyler and the Printed Image,", August 17-October 27, 2002 (Box 18)
    - "Pat Steir's 'Colors and Other Colors On Top',", September 28-December 8, 2002 (Box 18)
    - "Artistas de la Gente/Artists of the People: Mexican Prints of the 20th Century,", circa October 19, 2002 (Box 18)
    - "Masterworks of Chinese Painting: In Pursuit of Mist and Clouds,", October 12, 2002-January 5, 2003 (Box 18)
      (Berkeley Art Museum)
    - "Graphic Visions: German Expressionist Prints and Drawings,", circa April 6, 2003 (Box 18)
- Executive Files, 1945-2002
  Executive Files (1945-2002; 4.7 linear ft.) are divided into three subseries: Executive Committee Minutes, Director's Correspondence, and Conferences and Committees. Executive Committee Minutes document chiefly loans and acquisitions through purchase and gift, but include other museum business, policies and staff appointments. These files are restricted until July 1, 2024. Director's Correspondence, in keeping with the system maintained by UMMA, is filed according to location of the correspondent, excluding correspondence within the University of Michigan. These are grouped alphabetically by state, then by city, and finally by institution or organization. (Canada and other foreign countries follow the United States.) For example, to locate correspondence with the Walker Art Center, one would consult Minnesota--Minneapolis--Walker Art Center. Within these files, documents are arranged in reverse chronological order. The Conferences and Committees subseries contains a limited amount of material (correspondence and typewritten remarks) related to staff members' professional activities, including professional service and conference participation. These provide insight into museum philosophy at the time on training museum professionals, museum scholarship, and the loaning of works for special exhibitions.
  - Executive Committee minutes
    - 1945-1946 (Box 19)
      [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2024 ]
    - 1947 (Box 19)
    - 1953 (Box 19)
    - 1957 (Box 19)
    - 1958 (Box 19)
    - 1959 (Box 19)
    - 1960 (Box 19)
    - 1961 (Box 19)
    - 1962 (Box 19)
    - 1964 (Box 19)
    - 1965 (Box 19)
    - 1966 (Box 19)
    - 1967 (Box 19)
    - 1968 (Box 19)
    - 1969 (Box 19)
    - 1970 (Box 19)
    - 1971 (Box 19)
    - 1972 (Box 19)
    - 1973 (Box 19)
    - 1974 (Box 19)
    - 1975 (Box 19)
    - 1976 (Box 19)
    - 1977 (Box 19)
    - 1978 (Box 19)
    - 1979 (Box 19)
    - 1980 (Box 19)
    - 1981 (Box 19)
    - 1982 (Box 19)
    - 1983 (Box 19)
    - 1984 (Box 19)
    - 1985 (Box 19)
    - 1986 (Box 19)
    - 1987 (Box 19)
    - 1988 (Box 19)
    - 1989 (Box 19)
    - 1990 (Box 19)
    - 1991 (Box 19)
    - 1992 (Box 19)
    - 1993 (Box 19)
    - 1994 (Box 19)
    - 1995 (Box 19)
    - 1996 (Box 19)
    - 1997 (Box 19)
    - 1998 (Box 19)
    - 1999 (Box 19)
    - 2000 (Box 19)
    - 2001 (Box 19)
    - 2002 (Box 19)
  - Director's Correspondence
    - Alabama: General, 1984-1986 (Box 20)
    - Arizona: General, 1981-1990 (Box 20)
    - Arkansas: General, 1978 (Box 20)
    - California
      - Berkeley: University of California, Berkeley, University Art Museum, 1971-1996 (Box 20)
      - Los Angeles: Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1971-1988 (Box 20)
      - San Francisco: The Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco, 1971-1996 (Box 20)
      - General, 1967-1996 (Box 20)
    - Colorado: General, 1966-1999 (Box 20)
    - Connecticut
      - New Haven: Yale University, 1969-1988 (Box 20)
      - General, 1962-1992 (Box 20)
    - Delaware: General, 1972-1994 (Box 20)
    - District of Columbia
      - Freer Gallery, 1958-1988 (Box 20)
      - National Museum of African Art, 1983-1988 (Box 20)
      - National Museum of American Art, 1983-1995 (Box 20)
      - General, 1957-1993 (Box 20)
    - Florida: General, 1965-1992 (Box 20)
    - Georgia: General, 1970-1996 (Box 20)
    - Hawaii: General, 1982-1984 (Box 20)
    - Idaho: General, 1970-1992 (Box 20)
    - Illinois
      - Chicago: Art Institute of Chicago, 1953-1987 (Box 20)
      - General, 1961-2001 (Box 20)
    - Indiana
      - Bloomington: Indiana University, 1960-1976 (Box 20)
      - Indianapolis: Indianapolis Museum of Art, 1986-1993 (Box 20)
      - Notre Dame: University of Notre Dame, 1962-1993 (Box 20)
      - General, 1967-1994 (Box 20)
    - Iowa: General, 1957-1990 (Box 20)
    - Kansas
      - Lawrence: University of Kansas, 1963-1995 (Box 20)
      - General, 1965-1977 (Box 20)
    - Kentucky
      - Louisville: J. B. Speed Art Museum, 1963-1964 (Box 20)
      - General, 1957-1996 (Box 20)
    - Louisiana: General, 1983-1990 (Box 20)
    - Maine: General, 1972-1988 (Box 20)
    - Maryland
      - Baltimore
        - Baltimore Museum of Art, 1981-1987 (Box 20)
        - Walters Art Gallery, 1962-1990 (Box 20)
    - Massachusetts
      - Cambridge: Fogg Art Museum, Harvard University, 1973-1996 (Box 20)
      - Northampton: Smith College Museum of Art, 1972-1987 (Box 20)
      - South Hadley: Mount Holyoke College Art Museum, 1984 (Box 20)
      - Springfield: Museum of Fine Arts, 1984 (Box 20)
      - Williamstown: Williams College, 1989-1994 (Box 20)
      - Worcester: Worcester Art Museum, 1969-1972 (Box 20)
      - General, 1959-2001 (Box 20)
    - Michigan
      - Albion: Albion College, 1947-1993 (Box 20)
      - Alpena: Jesse Besser Museum, 1971-1976 (Box 20)
      - Ann Arbor
        - Ann Arbor Art Association, 1957-1978 (Box 20)
        - Historical Society of Michigan, 1983 (Box 20)
      - Battle Creek: Civic Art Center, 1963-1976 (Box 20)
      - Bloomfield Hills: Cranbrook Academy
        - 1972-1993 (Box 20)
        - 1966-1971 (Box 20)
        - 1946-1965 (Box 20)
      - Dearborn: Henry Ford Museum
        - 1972-1997 (Box 20)
        - 1963-1971 (Box 20)
        - 1952-1962 (Box 20)
      - Detroit
        - Detroit Historical Museum, 1957-1968 (Box 20)
        - Detroit Institute of Arts
          - 1986-2001 (Box 20)
          - 1975-1985 (Box 20)
          - 1969-1974 (Box 20)
          - 1963-1968 (Box 20)
          - 1958-1962 (Box 20)
          - 1946-1957 (Box 20)
        - Friends of Modern Art (DIA), 1962-1973 (Box 21)
        - Project Outreach (DIA), 1970 (Box 21)
        - Wayne State University, 1947-1986 (Box 21)
        - General, 1967-1984 (Box 21)
      - East Lansing
        - Michigan (State) Council for the Arts, 1966-1975 (Box 21)
        - Michigan State University/Michigan Agricultural College
          - 1968-1978 (Box 21)
          - 1967 (Box 21)
          - 1957-1966 (Box 21)
          - 1946-1952 (Box 21)
      - Flint: Flint Institute of Arts
        - 1968-1996 (Box 21)
        - 1947-1967 (Box 21)
      - Grand Rapids: Grand Rapids Art Museum
        - 1967-1991 (Box 21)
        - 1946-1966 (Box 21)
      - Holland: Hope College: De Pree Gallery, 1984 (Box 21)
      - Jackson: Ella Sharp Museum, 1969-1976 (Box 21)
      - Kalamazoo
        - Kalamazoo Institute of Arts
          - 1968-1986 (Box 21)
          - 1966-1967 (Box 21)
          - 1960-1965 (Box 21)
          - 1947-1959 (Box 21)
        - Western Michigan University, 1983 (Box 21)
      - Lansing: Michigan Historical Commission, 1955-1965 (Box 21)
      - Midland: Midland Art Association [Midland Arts Council], 1957-1992 (Box 21)
      - Muskegon
        - Hackley Art Gallery, 1950-1990 (Box 21)
        - Muskegon Museum of Art, 1990-1994 (Box 21)
      - Olivet: Olivet College, 1946-1976 (Box 21)
      - Rochester
        - Michigan State University Oak, 1962-1979 (Box 21)
        - Oakland University: Meadowbrook Gallery, 1986-1989 (Box 21)
      - Saginaw: Saginaw Art Museum, 1949-1978 (Box 21)
      - Traverse City: Dennos Center, 1996 (Box 21)
      - Ypsilanti: Eastern Michigan University, 1963-1985 (Box 21)
      - Michigan Cultural Commission
        - 1962-1963 (Box 21)
        - 1961 (Box 21)
        - 1960 (Box 21)
      - Michigan Museum Council
        - 1959-1961 (Box 21)
        - 1950-1958 (Box 21)
      - Michigan Museums Association, 1975-1977 (Box 21)
      - General
        - 1969-1996 (Box 21)
        - 1955-1968 (Box 21)
    - Minnesota
      - Minneapolis
        - Minneapolis Institute of Arts, 1967-1997 (Box 21)
        - University of Minnesota, University Gallery, 1965-1993 (Box 21)
        - Walker Art Center, 1987-1989 (Box 21)
      - General, 1993 (Box 21)
    - Missouri
      - Kansas City
        - Kansas City Art Institute, 1983 (Box 21)
        - William Rockhill Nelson Art Gallery, 1962-1964 (Box 21)
      - St. Louis: St. Louis Art Museum, 1964-1991 (Box 21)
      - General, 1984-1993 (Box 21)
    - Montana: General, 1982-1984 (Box 22)
    - Nebraska
      - Lincoln: University of Nebraska, 1962-1978 (Box 22)
      - General, 1991 (Box 22)
    - Nevada: General, 1984 (Box 22)
    - New Hampshire
      - Durham: University of New Hampshire, 1970-1973 (Box 22)
      - General, 1970-1992 (Box 22)
    - New Jersey
      - Montclair: Montclair Art Museum, 1986-1996 (Box 22)
      - New Brunswick: Rutgers, The State University, 1967-1977 (Box 22)
      - Princeton: Princeton University, 1989 (Box 22)
      - General, 1959-1990 (Box 22)
    - New Mexico: General, 1968-1985 (Box 22)
    - New York
      - Brooklyn: Brooklyn Museum, 1948-1996 (Box 22)
      - Buffalo: Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1957-1972 (Box 22)
      - Cooperstown: New York State Historical Association, 1966-1972 (Box 22)
      - New York City
        - Asia Society Gallery, 1984-1993 (Box 22)
        - The Center for African Art (Dr. Susan Vogel), 1984-1986 (Box 22)
        - Cooper Union Museum (Cooper Hewitt), 1955-1996 (Box 22)
        - Kress Foundation, 1961-1970 (Box 22)
        - Metropolitan Museum of Art
          - 1985-1996 (Box 22)
          - 1957-1984 (Box 22)
        - Museum of Modern Art, 1956-1995 (Box 22)
        - New York Public Library, 1984-1986 (Box 22)
        - Pierpont Morgan Library, 1984 (Box 22)
        - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1962-1983 (Box 22)
        - General, 1970-1999 (Box 22)
      - Purchase: Neuberger Museum, State University of New York, 1984-1993 (Box 22)
      - Rochester: University of Rochester, 1961-1983 (Box 22)
      - Stony Brook: State University of New York at Stony Brook, 1983 (Box 22)
      - Syracuse: Everson Museum of Art, 1964-1968 (Box 22)
      - General
        - 1974-1997 (Box 22)
        - 1957-1973 (Box 22)
    - North Carolina
      - Raleigh: North Carolina Museum of Art, 1981-1985 (Box 22)
      - General, 1966-1992 (Box 22)
    - North Dakota: General, 1993-1994 (Box 22)
    - Ohio
      - Akron: Akron Art Museum, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
      - Cleveland: Cleveland Museum of Art, 1963-1989 (Box 22)
      - Columbus
        - Columbus Museum of Art, 1983-1986 (Box 22)
        - Gallery of Fine Arts, 1951-1972 (Box 22)
        - Ohio State University, 1960-1986 (Box 22)
      - Dayton: Dayton Art Institute, 1957-1994 (Box 22)
      - Oberlin: Oberlin College, 1958-1994 (Box 22)
      - Toledo
        - Toledo Museum of Art
          - 1976-1998 (Box 22)
          - 1971-1975 (Box 22)
          - 1968-1970 (Box 22)
          - 1963-1967 (Box 22)
          - 1951-1962 (Box 22)
        - American Museum Education (visitors from abroad), 1970 (Box 22)
      - Youngstown: Butler Institute of American Art, 1964-1965 (Box 22)
      - General, 1965-1994 (Box 22)
    - Oklahoma: General, 1970-1992 (Box 23)
    - Oregon
      - Eugene: University of Oregon, 1964-1984 (Box 23)
      - Portland: Portland Art Association, 1984 (Box 23)
      - General, 1962-1993 (Box 23)
    - Pennsylvania
      - Philadelphia: Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1969-1990 (Box 23)
      - Pittsburgh: Museum of Art-Carnegie Institute, 1956-1987 (Box 23)
      - University Park: The Pennsylvania State University, 1984-1994 (Box 23)
      - General, 1969-1996 (Box 23)
    - Rhode Island
      - Providence: Rhode Island School of Design, 1962-1985 (Box 23)
      - General, 1958-1984 (Box 23)
    - South Carolina: General, 1958-1974 (Box 23)
    - Tennessee
      - Memphis: Brooks Memorial Art Gallery, 1987-1990 (Box 23)
      - General, 1961-1994 (Box 23)
    - Texas
      - Amarillo: Amarillo Art Center, 1983 (Box 23)
      - Austin: University of Texas, 1958-1983 (Box 23)
      - General, 1958-1997 (Box 23)
    - Utah: General, 1964-1991 (Box 23)
    - Vermont: General, 1964-1977 (Box 23)
    - Virginia: General, 1958-1978 (Box 23)
    - Washington
      - Seattle: University of Washington, 1964-1995 (Box 23)
      - General, 1958-1986 (Box 23)
    - Wisconsin
      - Madison
        - Madison Art Center, 1984 (Box 23)
        - University of Wisconsin, 1963-1996 (Box 23)
      - General, 1963-1993 (Box 23)
    - Wyoming: General, 1984-1990 (Box 23)
    - American Federation of Arts, 1976-1978 (Box 23)
    - Association of Art Museum Directors, 1981 (Box 23)
    - Canada
      - Ontario
        - Ottawa: National Gallery of Canada, 1966-1971 (Box 23)
        - Toronto
          - Art Gallery of Ontario, 1984-1993 (Box 23)
          - Art Gallery of Toronto, 1961-1964 (Box 23)
        - Windsor: Art Gallery of Windsor, 1984-1991 (Box 23)
      - General, 1964-1996 (Box 23)
    - England: General, 1961-1992 (Box 23)
    - Europe: General, 1966-1997 (Box 23)
    - Other Foreign: General, 1968-1995 (Box 23)
  - Conferences and Committees
    - Association of Art Museum Directors-Committee on Training Art Museum Directors, 1975-1978 (Box 23)
    - Conference for Small Art Museums (Heckscher Museum), 1970 (Box 23)
    - Michigan Museum Directors Conference, 1956; 1958 (Box 23)
    - Midwest Art History Society, 1981 (Box 23)
    - Midwest College Art Conference, 1964 (Box 23)
- Photographs, 1913-1998
  Photographs (1913-1998; 0.3 linear ft.) document the museum's facilities, both exterior and interior; its staff; and a small number of events throughout its history. Portraits of docents can be found within the Docent series, as well as additional photographs of staff members in the early 1990s. If exhibition installations are identified they are within the Exhibition Files series. Otherwise they are included within this series, under 'Galleries,' which also contains installation shots of the permanent collection galleries. The series includes various media: black and white and color prints, 35mm slides, 35mm negatives and glass plate negatives.